kingsurfproxy.com 2016-10-28

# KingSurfProxy | Free Czech Republic Service, Unblock Youtube, facebook, Twitter

### Privacy Policy

Our service may collect information about you during your visit. This document describes the information we collect and how it is used.

**Server Access Logs**

Our server logs all requests. The data recorded includes information provided by your browser (user agent and referring page) as well as the requested URI, the time and date and your IP address. The data recorded in these logs may be used for detecting and preventing abuse. We may also collate this data for statistical purposes.

**Service Logs**

The service provided on this website allows access to external, third-party websites. We may record your IP address and the websites you visit. The logs are used primarily for monitoring requests and ensuring no illegal activity is undertaken. Any violations of our terms of use may result in disclosure of the data recorded in our logs to an appropriate third party, which may include your Internet Service Provider (ISP) or local authorities. We may also be required, by law, to provide logs of our service and if requested, such data will be disclosed. We may also use service logs for stastical purposes.

**Cookies**

Our website stores a cookie on your computer, if allowed by your browser's privacy settings *. The cookie used by our service uniquely identifies you to the server and allows our website to remember your preferences.

We also use third-party advertising partners on our website. Advertisers may send you cookies or use web beacons. We have no control over cookies, web beacons or the information collected by our advertisers. Consult the third-party advertiser's privacy policy for more information on their practices.

The service we provide may attempt to forward third-party cookies from the websites you choose to browse. We have no control over indirect cookies and you are advised to consult the privacy policy of the applicable third-party website. If you do not wish to receive any such indirect cookies, please disable the "Allow Cookies" option.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet. To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html"). Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google's own privacy policies.

**Links to Advertisers Privacy Policies**

[Google's privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html) :: [Doubleclick's privacy policy](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/)

* For more information on configuring your browser, see [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1 "About Cookies") or the documentation for your browser. We are not responsible for the content of any third-party websites.

**Email Addresses**

This website does not require or collect your email address.

**Submitted Information**

We do not have any control over any information you submit to this or any other website through us. Any information submitted is entirely at your own risk and we cannot be held responsible for any consequences of your actions or inactions. This website DOES NOT use a secure connection for anything and you submit any and all personal details completely at your own risk.

This website does not offer any warrenty or guarantees of any kind, nor should any be implied or assumed.

We do try to conform to all our advertise's policies and we will do what is necessary to stay within their terms. This privacy policy is subject to change without notice and it is your responsabilty to keep up to date with our requirements.
